(Sheldon:)Penny.
(Penny:)What?
(Sheldon(Knock, knock, knock):)Zucchini bread.
(Penny:)Oh, thank you.
- May I come in?
- No.
(Sheldon:)I see. Apparently, my earlier inquiry...
(Sheldon:)...regarding you and Leonard
crossed some sort of line.
(Sheldon:)I apologize.
(Penny:)Oh, thank you.
(Sheldon:)So have you and I returned
to a social equilibrium?
- Yes.
- Great.
(Sheldon:)- New topic.
- Mm.
(Sheldon:)Where are you in your menstrual cycle?
(Penny:)- What?
- I've been doing some research online...
(Sheldon:)...and, apparently, female primates...
You know, uh, apes, chimpanzees, you.
(Sheldon:)...they find their mate more desirable
when he's courted by another female.
(Sheldon:)Now, this effect is intensified
when the rival female...